Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs
1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
PC 195
Washington State University. Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center
4.25 Linear feet of shelf space 8 Boxes
Agricultural research photos from the Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center, or IAREC, formerly the Irrigation Experiment Station, in Prosser, Washington.
The Irrigation Experiment Station was authorized by the state legislature in 1917, and opened at Prosser, WA on May 24, 1919. In 1965 the name was changed to the Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center (IAREC).
Photographs and negatives, of approximately 2600 images, documenting the work and environs of the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center (IAREC) / Irrigation Experiment Station in Prosser, and of its researchers and staff.
The collection is retained primarily in the organization in which it came to the MASC. Materials produced by WSU Prosser staff make up the vast majority of the collection, and are organized chronologically using identifiers created at the time. At the end of that chronology are a few items where the date is unknown. Following that series is a smaller series of photographs taken by the federal government (USDA), using the same organizational system. At the end is a series of index cards which contains identifying information for many of the photographs, usually taken from the envelopes in which the images are still housed.
The original envelopes in which the photographs were housed all have identifiers, in which the first two digits indicate the year of creation, followed by numbers indicating the order in which the photos were collected in that year. Those identifiers serve as the item numbers in this collection.
Description of the material comes primarily from notes on the original photographic sleeves. The descriptions on the index cards appear to also come from the envelopes. Larry Wright added some names to the descriptions based on his and others’ personal recognition of individuals.
Prior to donation, and with WSU’s permission, Larry Wright scanned 347 selected images and uploaded them to the Washington State Library’s Washington Rural Heritage project. In the Rural Heritage metadata, the original file number in the Source item specifications matches to the item identifiers in this collection. Their WSUP### identifiers have been incorporated into the end of each description in the container list.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Larry Wright of Prosser donated this collection to the Washington State University Libraries on May 17, 2021, where they were retained as UPC 2021-01. Wright states that a file cabinet in the basement of a building at WSU-Prosser contained several drawers of old negatives taken by WSU employees as part of their jobs. In 2012 he moved the cabinet from the WSU-Prosser building to his own home for safe keeping, as they were afraid someone would discard the negatives, or that the basement where the negatives were stored would flood as it had previously done. Dorothy Evans and Wright subsequently cataloged the negatives.
Irrigation Branch Experiment Station (Prosser) Reports, 1919-1960 (Archives 76)
Irrigation Branch Experiment Station Records, 1910-1979 (Archives 200)
Irrigated Agriculture Research and Experiment Center (Prosser) Grapes/Wine Research Records, 1940-1984 (Archives 214)
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Wright, Larry; Evans, Dorothy
Washington State University. Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center -- Photographs; Washington State University. Irrigation Branch Experiment Station -- Photographs; State College of Washington. Irrigation Branch Experiment Station -- Photographs; Washington State University. Irrigation Branch Experiment Station; State College of Washington. Irrigation Branch Experiment Station
Prosser (Wash.) -- Photographs
Agricultural experiment stations -- Research -- Washington (State); Agriculture -- Experimentation -- History -- Photographs; Irrigation farming -- Washington (State) -- Photographs; Agriculture -- Photographs
Agriculture; Colleges and University; Photographs
- Series 1: Images created by WSU-Prosser staff, 1919-1969
  - Subseries 1: Dated images, 1919-1969
    - Digging ? Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1919 (Box 1, Item 19.001)
    - Foundation Forms for first House on Experiment Station. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP353. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.001)
    - Experiment Station. Forms for First House. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.002)
    - First House Constructed on Experiment Station. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP354. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.003)
    - Construction of Second? House on Experiment Station. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP355. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.005)
    - Drilling the Well. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.007)
    - Machine Shed and Well Drilling Outfit. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.009)
    - Brood Sow. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.010)
    - Brood Sow. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.011)
    - Brood Sow. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.012)
    - Brood Sow. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.013)
    - Team - Mike and Duke. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.014)
    - Sage Brush Raked up Before Plowing. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.016)
    - Clearing Sagebrush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.017)
    - Clearing Sagebrush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.018)
    - Clearing Sagebrush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1920 (Box 1, Item 20.019)
    - Lamb Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP010. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.001)
    - Lamb Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.002)
    - Lamb Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.003)
    - Lambs on Feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.004)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.005)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.006)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.007)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.008)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.009)
    - Type of lambs fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP011. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.010)
    - Type of lamb fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.011)
    - Type of lamb fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.012)
    - Pigs. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. WSUP012. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.013)
    - Hogs. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.014)
    - Hogs. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.015)
    - Hogs. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.016)
    - Hogs. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.017)
    - Feeder's Day. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.020)
    - Sunflowers. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP013. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.021)
    - Building First Silo. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.022)
    - Field day. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP014. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.024)
    - Plowing with Six Horses. "They are mules!" was obviously written later on envelope. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP015. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.026)
    - Columbia River at Flood Stage. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.028)
    - Umatilla Railroad Bridge at Flood Stage. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.029)
    - Station Buildings and Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP016. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.031)
    - Duke. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP017. 1921 (Box 1, Item 21.032)
    - Official Visit of U.S.D.A. Men. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP018. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.002)
    - Hogs. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.004)
    - Hogs. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.005)
    - Cottage on Station. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP019. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.007)
    - Lambs on sweet clover hay. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922-03-04 (Box 1, Item 22.008)
    - Lambs watering at Yakima River. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP020. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.009)
    - Fat lambs loaded on trucks. Actually railroad cars. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.010)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922-03-04 (Box 1, Item 22.011)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.012)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.013)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1922 (Box 1, Item 22.014)
    - Standing Alfalfa Hay. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP021. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.001)
    - Alfalfa hay and shock. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.002)
    - Les Robertson, Jerry Satola, George McWhirter. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP022. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.003)
    - Soil thermograph. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.004)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.005)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.007)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.008)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.009)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.010)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.011)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.012)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.013)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.014)
    - Lambs on Feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP023. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.016)
    - Lambs in feed lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.018)
    - Lambs on Feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.019)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.020)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.021)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.022)
    - Lamb Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.023)
    - Sweet potato plant. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.024)
    - Sweet potato plant. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.025)
    - Sweet potato plant. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.026)
    - Sweet potato plant. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.027)
    - Sweet potato plant. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.028)
    - Hog House Construction. Amon and Wood. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP024. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.029)
    - Cattle Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.031)
    - Time of planting potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1923 (Box 1, Item 23.060)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.001)
    - Lambs on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.002)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.003)
    - Feeder's Day. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP025. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.004)
    - Feeder's Day - Official Visitors. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP026. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.006)
    - Feeder's Day. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP027. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.007)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush Scene. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.008)
    - Alfalfa hay and shack. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.010)
    - Alfalfa Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP028. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.011)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP029. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.012)
    - Binding Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP030. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.014)
    - Binding Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP031. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.015)
    - Binding Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP032. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.016)
    - Binding wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP033. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.017)
    - Wheat Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP324. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.019)
    - Wheat Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.020)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.021)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP034. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.023)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.024)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.025)
    - Two Silos. Koenig on envelope. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.028)
    - Cattle Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.029)
    - Steer Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.030)
    - Steer Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.031)
    - Steer Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.032)
    - Steer Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.033)
    - Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.180)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1924 (Box 1, Item 24.220)
    - Stacking Hay. No number on 3.5x5.5 neg. Print. WSUP035. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.00a)
    - Stacking Hay. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP036. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.00b)
    - Holstein Calves. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.001)
    - Holstein Calves. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.002)
    - Holstein Calves. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.003)
    - Calf on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.004)
    - Calf on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.005)
    - Calf on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.006)
    - Calf on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.007)
    - Calf on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.008)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.009)
    - Type of cattle fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.010)
    - Cattle on Feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.011)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.012)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.013)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.014)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.015)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.016)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.017)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.018)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.019)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.020)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.021)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.022)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.022)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.023)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.023)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.024)
    - Cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.024)
    - Dairy cattle on pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.025)
    - Dairy cattle on pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.025)
    - Dairy cows on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.026)
    - Dairy cows on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.026)
    - Dairy cows on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1925-06-17 (Box 1, Item 25.027)
    - Dairy cows on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925-06-17 (Box 1, Item 25.027)
    - Weighing Cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. No print. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.029)
    - Cattle Crossing Prosser Bridge. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP037. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.031)
    - Seed Bed Preparation. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.033)
    - Seed Bed Preparation. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP038. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.034)
    - Seed Bed Preparation. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP039. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.036)
    - Seed Bed Preparation. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP040. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.037)
    - Seed Bed Preparation. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP041. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.039)
    - Alfalfa Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP325. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.040)
    - Cutting Alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP042. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.041)
    - Hauling Alfalfa Hay to Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP043. 1925-07-24 (Box 1, Item 25.042)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP044. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.043)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP045. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.044)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP046. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.045)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP326. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.046)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP047. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.048)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.049)
    - Hay Weighing Scales. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.051)
    - Feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.052)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.053)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.054)
    - Type of lambs fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.055)
    - Type of lambs fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.056)
    - Type of lambs fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.057)
    - Type of lambs fed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.058)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.059)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.060)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.061)
    - Lamb feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.062)
    - Corn field pastured by lambs. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.063)
    - Grain troughs for sheep. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.064)
    - Grain troughs for sheep. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.065)
    - Mowing wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP048. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.066)
    - Mowing wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP049. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.068)
    - Mowing wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP050. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.069)
    - Ditching with Mormon Ditcher. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP052. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.072)
    - Harrowing. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP053. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.073)
    - Poultry Houses. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.074)
    - Collins White Cultivator Team. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP054. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.075)
    - Intake of Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP327. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.076)
    - De-Horning Chute. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP055. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.077)
    - Cultivating Spuds. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP056. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.078)
    - Steer Feeding. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.079)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1925 (Box 1, Item 25.080)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.001)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.002)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.003)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.004)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.005)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.006)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.007)
    - North of Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.008)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.009)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.010)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.011)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.012)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.013)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.014)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.015)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.016)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.017)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.018)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.019)
    - Sage brush north of experiment station. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.020)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.021)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.022)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.023)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.024)
    - North of Experiment Station. Sage Brush. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.025)
    - Pullman. Laboratory Equipment for decomposition trials. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP057. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.026)
    - Pullman, Laboratory Equipment for decomposition trials. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP058. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.029)
    - Pullman, Laboratory Equipment for decomposition trials. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.030)
    - Pullman, Laboratory Equipment for decomposition trials. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP059. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.031)
    - Field Day. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.032)
    - Field Day. "Singleton WHROT" written on 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.033)
    - Field day. "Janson Trees" on 3.5x5.5 negative. WSUP328. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.034)
    - City Park - Horshoe Pitching. Field Day. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP060. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.035)
    - Field day. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP061. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.036)
    - Building second silo. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP062. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.038)
    - Building se.cond silo. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.039)
    - Building second silo. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP063. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.040)
    - Silo Building Crew. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP064. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.042)
    - Poultry Houses. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP065. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.043)
    - Feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.044)
    - Feed Lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.045)
    - Feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.046)
    - Feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.047)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.048)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.049)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.050)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.051)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.052)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.053)
    - 112. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.054)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.055)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.056)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP066. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.057)
    - Lambs in Feed Lot. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.058)
    - Corn field pastured with lambs for weed control. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.059)
    - Binding Corn. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.060)
    - Binding Corn. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP067. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.061)
    - Binding Corn. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.062)
    - Binding Corn. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.063)
    - Sweet Clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.064)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP068. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.065)
    - Mowing alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP069. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.066)
    - Mowing Alfalfa. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.066)
    - Jenkin Wheat. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.067)
    - Cultivating Wheat. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP070. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.068)
    - Wheat crop from station. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.069)
    - Potato Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.070)
    - Cultivating potatoes. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP071. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.071)
    - Weighing Cattle, C. C. Wright. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.072)
    - Weighing Cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.073)
    - Holstein Herd Sire. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.074)
    - Dairy cattle on pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.075)
    - Cattle on sweet clover pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.076)
    - Beef cattle in stock yards. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.077)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.077)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.079)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.080)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.081)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.082)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.083)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.084)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.085)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.086)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.087)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.088)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.089)